Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- U.S. Supreme Court Case Files, 1972-1974
  - 1971 October Term (January 1972-September 1972) and 1972 October Term (October 1972-September 1973), 1972-1973
    - Charles Joseph Kastigar and Michael Gorean Stewart v. United States (Box-folder 22: 70-117)
    - Bob Bullock v. Van Phillip Carter (Box-folder 22: 70-128)
    - United States v. Scotland Neck City Board of Education (Box-folder 22: 70-130)
      See also case 70-187
    - United States v. United States District Court for the Eastern District of Michigan, Southern Division (Box-folder 22: 70-153)
    - Elliot L. Richardson, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Radie Wright (Box-folder 22: 70-161)
      See also case 70-5211
    - Pattie Black Cotton v. Scotland Neck City Board of Education (Box-folder 22: 70-187)
      Found in case 70-130
    - Pecola Annette Wright v. Council of the City of Emporia (Box-folder 22: 70-188)
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc. v. New Hampshire Aeronautics Commission (Box-folder 22: 70-212)
      Found in case 70-99
    - Mortimer M. Caplin v. The Marine Midland Grace Trust Company of New York (Box-folder 22: 70-220)
    - Central Hardware Company v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 22: 70-223)
    - Robert B. Carleson v. Nancy Remillard (Box-folder 22: 70-250)
    - Lionel Adolph Joseph v. United States (Box-folder 22: 70-251)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Robert Scrivener, dba AA Electric Company (Box-folder 22: 70-267)
    - United States v. Florida East Coast Railway Company (Box-folder 23: 70-279)
    - Frederick E. Adams v. Robert Williams (Box-folder 23: 70-283)
    - Iowa Beef Packers, Inc. v. Edward D. Thompson (Box-folder 23: 70-286)
    - First City Bank v. Banco Nacional de Cuba (Box-folder 24: 70-295)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue v. First Security Bank of Utah (Box-folder 24: 70-305)
    - Brunette Machine Works Ltd. v. Kockum Industries, Inc. (Box-folder 24: 70-314)
    - George William Milton v. Louie L. Wainwright, Director, Florida Divisions of Corrections (Box-folder 24: 70-5012)
    - Jon Richard Argersinger v. Raymond Hamlin, Sheriff, Leon County, Florida (Box-folder 24: 70-5015)
    - Love v. The Pullman Company (Box-folder 24: 70-5033)
      See also case 70-37
    - John Adams v. State of Illinois (Box-folder 24: 70-5038)
    - Margarita Fuentes v. Robert L. Shevin, Attorney General of Florida (Box-folder 24: 70-5039)
      See also case 70-5138
    - Raymond Smith and Melvin McClain v. Florida (Box-folder 24: 70-5055)
    - Dorothy Lynch v. Household Finance Corporation (Box-folder 24: 70-5058)
    - Thomas Kirby v. State of Illinois (Box-folder 24: 70-5061)
    - Ruth Jefferson v. Burton G. Hackney, (2 folders) (Box-folder 25: 70-5064)
    - Harper & Holmes v. Illinois (Box-folder 25: 70-5072)
    - Jack Boyd v. A. L. Dutton (Box-folder 25: 70-5075)
    - Richard Grayned v. City of Rockford (Box-folder 25: 70-5106)
    - Willie Mae Weber v. Aetna Casualty & Surety Company (Box-folder 26: 70-5112)
    - Dennis Stephen Duncan v. State of Tennessee (Box-folder 26: 70-5122)
    - Paul Parham v. Americo V. Cortese (Box-folder 26: 70-5138)
      Found in case 70-5039
    - Radie Wright v. Elliot L. Richardson (Box-folder 26: 70-5211)
      Found in case 70-161
    - Albert Delanor Murel v. Baltimore City Criminal Court (Box-folder 26: 70-5276)
    - James Thomas Bell v. State of Kentucky (Box-folder 26: 70-5304)
    - Mallie Lewis v. City of New Orleans (Box-folder 26: 70-5323)
      Found in 71-1044
    - Otis Loper v. George J. Beto, Director, Texas Department of Corrections (Box-folder 26: 70-5388)
    - James R. James, Judicial Administrator v. David E. Strange (Box-folder 26: 71-11)
    - Richard G. Kleindienst, Attorney General of the United States v. Ernest Mandel (Box-folder 26: 71-16)
    - Curtis C. Flood v. Bowie K. Kuhn (Box-folder 26: 71-32)
    - California v. Robert LaRue (Box-folder 26: 71-36)
    - International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 150, AFL-CIO v. Flair Builders, Inc. (Box-folder 26: 71-41)
    - United States v. Leon Anthony Boswell (Box-folder 26: 71-81)
    - John A. Strait v. Melvin R. Laird, Secretary of Defense (Box-folder 27: 71-83)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company v. Erie Lackawanna Railroad Company (Box-folder 27: 71-107)
    - David Gelbard and Sidney Parnas v. United States (Box-folder 27: 71-110)
      See also case 71-263
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Burns International Security Services, Inc., (2 folders) (Box-folder 27: 71-123)
      See also case 71-198
    - Board of Regents of State Colleges v. David F. Roth (Box-folder 28: 71-162)
      Found in case 70-36
    - Burns International Security Services, Inc. v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 28: 71-198)
      Found in case 71-123
    - Peggy J. Connor v. John Bell Williams, Governor of Mississippi (Box-folder 28: 71-221)
    - Harold R. Swenson v. James William Stidham (Box-folder 28: 71-224)
    - United States v. Allegheny-Ludlum Steel Corporation (Box-folder 28: 71-227)
    - United States v. Antonio Dionisio (Box-folder 28: 71-229)
      See also case 71-850
    - Vincent R. Mancusi v. William C. Stubbs (Box-folder 28: 71-237)
    - In the Matter of Larry Little (Box-folder 28: 71-244)
    - William Rabe v. State of Washington (Box-folder 28: 71-247)
    - Grubbs, dba T. R. Grubbs Tire & Appliance v. General Electric Credit Corp. (Box-folder 28: 71-257)
    - United States v. Jogues Egan and Anne Elizabeth Walsh (Box-folder 28: 71-263)
      Found in case 71-110
    - Melvin R. Laird, Secretary of Defense v. Arlo Tatum, (2 folders) (Box-folder 29: 71-288)
    - Oliver A. Rosengrant v. Melvin R. Laird, Secretary of Defense (Box-folder 29: 71-298)
    - Andrew v. Louisville & Nashville (Box-folder 29: 71-300)
    - United States v. Marian A. Byrum, Executrix Under the Last Will and Testament of Milliken C. Byrum (Box-folder 29: 71-308)
    - Deepsouth Packing Co., Inc. v. The Laitram Corporation (Box-folder 29: 71-315)
    - M/S Bremen and Unterweser Reederei, GMBN v. Zapata Off-Shore Company (Box-folder 29: 71-322)
    - Tidewater Oil Co. v. United States and Phillips Petroleum Company (Box-folder 29: 71-336)
    - Joseph Colombo v. State of New York (Box-folder 29: 71-352)
    - Mahan, Secretary, State Board of Elections v. Howell, (2 folders) (Box-folder 30: 71-364)
      See also case 71-373
    - City of Virginia Beach v. Howell (Box-folder 30: 71-373)
      Found in case 71-364
    - Lewis Colten v. Commonwealth of Kentucky (Box-folder 30: 71-404)
    - Lake Carriers' Association v. Ralph A. MacMullan (Box-folder 30: 71-422)
    - Catherine J. Healy v. F. Don James (Box-folder 30: 71-452)
    - Joseph M. Kadans v. Jon R. Collins. Application A-784 (Box-folder 30: 71-463)
    - Robert Gottschalk, Acting Commissioner of Patents v. Gary R. Benson and Arthur C. Tabbot (Box-folder 31: 71-485)
    - Lloyd Corporation, Ltd. v. Donald M. Tanner (Box-folder 31: 71-492)
    - Clarence Ward v. Village of Monroeville (Box-folder 31: 71-496)
    - Robert Olff, a Minor v. East Side Union High School District (Box-folder 31: 71-498)
    - United States v. Midwest Video Corporation (Box-folder 31: 71-506)
    - Keyes v. School District 1, Denver, Colorado, (2 folders) (Box-folder 31: 71-507)
    - Combs v. United States (Box-folder 31: 71-517)
    - Vivian Spencer v. CEO George F. Kugler (Box-folder 31: 71-519)
    - United States v. Standard Oil Company of California (Box-folder 31: 71-527)
    - Native American Church of Navajoland Inc. v. Arizona Corporation Commission (Box-folder 31: 71-533)
    - United States v. Chester Fuller (Box-folder 32: 71-559)
    - District of Columbia v. Melvin Carter (Box-folder 32: 71-564)
    - United States v. Christian Echoes National Ministry Inc. (Box-folder 32: 71-565)
    - Laird, Secretary of Defense v. Nelms (Box-folder 32: 71-573)
    - Linda Gomez, Individually and as Next Friend of Zoraida Gomez v. Francisco Ocasio Perez (Box-folder 32: 71-575)
    - William S. Neil v. Archie Nathaniel Biggers (Box-folder 32: 71-586)
    - State of California v. Judith Krivda and Roger T. Minor (Box-folder 32: 71-651)
    - Thomas S. Gibson v. L. M. Berryhill (Box-folder 32: 71-653)
    - United States v. Glaxo Group Limited, (2 folders) (Box-folder 32: 71-666)
    - Executive Jet Aviation Inc. v. City of Cleveland, Ohio (Box-folder 33: 71-678)
    - Lehnhausen, Director, Department of Local Government Affairs of Illinois v. Lake Shore Auto Parts Co. (Box-folder 33: 71-685)
      See also case 71-691
    - Edward J. Barrett County Clerk of Cook County, Illinois v. Clemens K. Shapiro (Box-folder 33: 71-691)
      Found in case 71-685
    - Illinois v. Somerville, (4 folders) (Box-folder 33: 71-692)
    - United States v. First National Bancorporation, Inc. (Box-folder 33: 71-703)
    - Paul J. Trafficante v. Metropolitan Life Insurance Company (Box-folder 33: 71-708)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Granite State Joint Board, Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1029, AFL-CIO (Box-folder 33: 71-711)
    - Paul D. McGinnis, Commissioner of Correction, State of New York v. James Royster (Box-folder 33: 71-718)
    - Merle R. Schneckloth, Superintendent, California Conservation Center v. Robert Clyde Bustamonte (Box-folder 34: 71-732)
    - Mescalero, Apache Tribe v. Franklin Jones, Commissioner of the Bureau of Revenue of the State of New Mexico (Box-folder 34: 71-738)
    - United States v. Robert William Kras (Box-folder 34: 71-749)
    - Menna v. United States (Box-folder 34: 71-772)
    - Dorothy Taylor v. John J. McKeithen, Governor of Louisiana (Box-folder 34: 71-784)
    - Hughes Tool Co. v. Trans World Airlines, Inc. (Box-folder 34: 71-827)
      See also case 71-830
    - Leila Mourning v. Family Publications Service, Inc. (Box-folder 34: 71-829)
    - Tran World Airlines v. Hughes Tool Company (Box-folder 34: 71-830)
      Found in case 71-827
    - Rosalind McClanahan v. State Tax Commission of Arizona (Box-folder 34: 71-834)
    - Paul P. Erlenbaugh v. United States (Box-folder 34: 71-839)
    - United States v. Richard J. Mara aka Richard J. Marasovich (Box-folder 34: 71-850)
      Found in case 71-229
    - Evco, dba Evco Instructional Designs v. Franklin Jones, Commissioner of the Bureau of Revenue of the State of New Mexico (Box-folder 34: 71-857)
    - Thomas Ricci v. Chicago Mercantile Exchange (Box-folder 35: 71-858)
    - United Air Lines, Inc. v. George E. Mahin (Box-folder 35: 71-862)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. v. Democratic National Committee, (2 folders) (Box-folder 35: 71-863)
      See also cases 71-864, 71-865, 71-866
    - Federal Communications Commission v. Business Executives' Move for Vietnam Peace (Box-folder 35: 71-864)
      Found in case 71-863. See also cases 71-865, 71-866.
    - Post-Newsweek Stations, Capital Area, Inc. v. Business Executives' Move for Vietnam Peace (Box-folder 35: 71-865)
      Found in case 71-863. See also cases 71-864, 71-866.
    - American Broadcasting Companies, Inc. v. Democratic National Committee (Box-folder 35: 71-866)
      Found in case 71-863. See also cases 71-864, 71-865.
    - United States v. Falstaff Brewing Corporation, (2 folders) (Box-folder 35, 36: 71-873)
    - Heublein, Inc. v. South Carolina Tax Commission (Box-folder 36: 71-879)
    - Lillian V. Couch v. United States and Edward F. Jennings (Box-folder 36: 71-889)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. International Van Lines (Box-folder 36: 71-895)
    - Union Oil Company of California v. The Tugboat San Jacinto (Box-folder 36: 71-900)
    - Environmental Protection Agency v. Patsy T. Mink (Box-folder 36: 71-909)
    - Almota Farmers Elevator and Warehouse Company v. United States (Box-folder 36: 71-951)
    - Otter Tail Power Company v. United States (Box-folder 36: 71-991)
    - Michigan v. Payne (Box-folder 37: 71-1005)
    - Samuel Bronston v. United States (Box-folder 37: 71-1011)
    - Federal Power Commission v. Louisiana Power & Light Company (Box-folder 37: 71-1016)
      See also case 71-1040
    - Mike Gravel, United States Senator v. United States (Box-folder 37: 71-1017)
      See also case 71-1026
    - Employees of the Department of Public Health & Welfare, State of Missouri v. Department of Public Health & Welfare, State of Missouri (Box-folder 37: 71-1021)
    - United States v. James A. Basye (Box-folder 37: 71-1022)
    - Sixty-Seventh Minnesota State Senate v. Richard A. Beens (Box-folder 37: 71-1024)
      See also case 71-1145
    - United States v. Mike Gravel, United States Senator (Box-folder 37: 71-1026)
      Found in case 71-1017
    - Leonard Tonasket v. Washington (Box-folder 37: 71-1031)
    - United Gas Pipe Line Company v. Louisiana Power & Light Co. (Box-folder 37: 71-1040)
      Found in case 71-1016
    - Heller v. New York (Box-folder 37: 71-1043)
    - David A. Rosenfeld v. New Jersey (Box-folder 37: 71-1044)
      See also case 70-5323
    - Paris Adult Theatre v. Lewis R. Slaton, District Attorney, Atlanta Judicial Circuit (Box-folder 38: 71-1051)
    - Kern County Land Co. v. Occidental Petroleum Corp. (Box-folder 38: 71-1059)
    - Associated Enterprises, Inc., and Johnston Fuel Liners v. Toltee Watershed Improvement District (Box-folder 38: 71-1069)
    - Reubin O'D. Askew v. The American Waterways Operators, Inc. (Box-folder 38: 71-1082)
    - Indiana Employment Security Division v. Essie D. Burney (Box-folder 38: 71-1119)
    - Harry Roaden v. Commonwealth of Kentucky (Box-folder 38: 71-1134)
    - Murray Tillman v. Wheaton-Haven Recreation Association, Inc. (Box-folder 38: 71-1136)
    - Sixty-Seventh Minnesota State Senate v. Richard A. Beens (Box-folder 38: 71-1145)
      Found in case 71-1024
    - Gulf States Utilities Company v. Federal Power Commission (Box-folder 38: 71-1178)
    - John Thomas Flower v. United States (Box-folder 38: 71-1180)
    - Mattz v. Arnett, Director, Department of Fish and Game (Box-folder 38: 71-1182)
    - Donald Goldstein, Ruth Koven, and Donald Koven v. State of California (Box-folder 39: 71-1192)
    - United States v. Travis Paul Enmons (Box-folder 39: 71-1193)
    - Jule M. Sugarman v. Patrick McL. Dougall (Box-folder 39: 71-1222)
      See also case 71-1336
    - John R. Gagnon v. Gerald H. Scarpelli (Box-folder 39: 71-1225)
    - United States v. Charles J. Ash (Box-folder 39: 71-1255)
    - James B. Bradley, Jr. v. United States (Box-folder 39: 71-1304)
    - Howard Alexander v. Commonwealth of Virginia (Box-folder 39: 71-1315)
    - San Antonio Independent School District v. Demetrio P. Rodriguez, (2 folders) (Box-folder 39: 71-1332)
    - In re Application of Fre Le Poole Griffiths for Admission to the Bar (Box-folder 40: 71-1336)
      See also case 71-1222
    - Russell G. Oswald, Commissioner of Correctional Services v. Eugene Rodriguez (Box-folder 40: 71-1369)
    - Pedro J. Rosario v. Nelson Rockefeller, Governor of the State of New York (Box-folder 40: 71-1371)
    - John W. Warner, Secretary of the Navy v. John W. Flemings (Box-folder 40: 71-1398)
      Found in case 71-6314
    - Booster Lodge 405, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO v. National Labor Relations Board (Box-folder 40: 71-1417)
    - Kaplan v. California (Box-folder 40: 71-1422)
    - Kirby J. Hensley v. Municipal Court, San Jose-Milpitas Judicial District, Santa Clara County, State of California (Box-folder 40: 71-1428)
    - Roland V. Colgrove v. James F. Battin, United States District Judge for the District of Montana (Box-folder 40: 71-1442)
    - Salyer Land Company v. Tulare Lake Basin Water Storage District (Box-folder 40: 71-1456)
    - United States v. Little Lake Misere Land Company, Inc. (Box-folder 41: 71-1459)
    - Lemon v. Kurtzman, Superintendent of Public Instruction of Pennsylvania (Box-folder 41: 71-1470)
    - J. Brian Gaffney v. Theodore R. Cummings (Box-folder 41: 71-1476)
      See also case 72-147
    - Hunt v. McNair, Governor of South Carolina (Box-folder 41: 71-1523)
    - Earl L. Butz, Secretary of Agriculture v. Glover Livestock Commission Company, Inc. (Box-folder 41: 71-1545)
    - John J. Gilligan, Governor of Ohio v. Craig Morgan (Box-folder 41: 71-1553)
    - Edmund G. Brown, Jr., Secretary of State of California v. Raymond G. Chote (Box-folder 41: 71-1583)
    - United States v. Richard Russell (Box-folder 41: 71-1585)
    - Peter J. Brennan, Secretary of Labor v. Arnheim and Neely, Inc. (Box-folder 41: 71-1598)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. The Boeing Company (Box-folder 42: 71-1607)
    - White, Secretary of State of Texas v. Weiser (Box-folder 42: 71-1623)
    - City of Burbank v. Lockheed Air Terminal Inc. (Box-folder 42: 71-1637)
    - William M. Broadrick v. State of Oklahoma (Box-folder 42: 71-1639)
    - Federal Maritime Commission v. Seatrain Lines Inc. (Box-folder 42: 71-1647)
    - United States v. Douglas B. Cartwright, as Executor of the Estate of Ethel B. Bennett (Box-folder 42: 71-1665)
    - James E. Gustafson v. State of Florida (Box-folder 42: 71-1669)
    - Sharron A. Frontiero and Joseph Frontiero v. Elliot L. Richardson, Secretary of Defense (Box-folder 42: 71-1694)
    - United States v. Cecil J. Bishop (Box-folder 42: 71-1698)
    - Dean Rene Peters v. C. P. Kiff (Box-folder 42: 71-5078)
    - Harold Eugene Huffman v. Faye I. Boersen (Box-folder 43: 71-5097)
    - John J. Morrissey and G. Donald Booher v. Lou V. Brewer (Box-folder 43: 71-5103)
    - Ham v. South Carolina (Box-folder 43: 71-5139)
    - Edward Lee McNeil v. Director, Patuxent Institution (Box-folder 43: 71-5144)
    - Charles O. Dukes v. Warden, Connecticut State Prison (Box-folder 43: 71-5172)
    - Willie Mae Barker v. John W. Wingo (Box-folder 43: 71-5255)
    - Donald L. Brooks v. State of Tennessee, (2 folders) (Box-folder 43: 71-5313)
    - Francis A. Keeble v. United States (Box-folder 43: 71-5323)
    - Robert Joe Robins v. United States (Box-folder 43: 71-5405)
    - George Martin Bradley v. United States (Box-folder 43: 71-5431)
    - Gerald Shadwick v. City of Tampa (Box-folder 43: 71-5445)
    - William Polk v. United States (Box-folder 43: 71-5459)
    - Edward McGray v. United States (Box-folder 43: 71-5547)
    - Fred A. Cruz v. George J. Beto, Director, Texas Department of Corrections (Box-folder 44: 71-5552)
    - Rudy Gonzales v. George J. Beto, Director, Texas Department of Corrections (Box-folder 44: 71-5580)
    - John R. Kois v. State of Wisconsin (Box-folder 44: 71-5625)
    - Doris Philpott and William Wilkes v. Essex County Welfare Board (Box-folder 44: 71-5656)
    - Johnson v. New York State Education Department (Box-folder 44: 71-5685)
    - Thomas W. Lippitt v. Joseph A. Cipollone (Box-folder 44: 71-5729)
    - Leon Chambers v. State of Mississippi (Box-folder 44: 71-5908)
    - Wardius v. Oregon (Box-folder 44: 71-6042)
    - Anthony Louis Tacon v. State of Arizona, (2 folders) (Box-folder 44: 71-6060)
    - Linda R. S. v. Richard D. (Box-folder 44: 71-6078)
    - Joseph Everette Brown and Thomas Dean Smith v. United States (Box-folder 44: 71-6193)
    - Samuel Ed Robinson v. William S. Neil (Box-folder 45: 71-6272)
    - Condrado Almeida-Sanchez v. United States (Box-folder 45: 71-6278)
    - James Roy Gosa v. J. A. Mayden (Box-folder 45: 71-6314)
      See also case 71-1398
    - Andrew C. Goosby v. Maurice Osser (Box-folder 45: 71-6316)
    - John Doe v. John L. McMillan, (2 folders) (Box-folder 45: 71-6356)
    - Ivan v. City of New York (Box-folder 45: 71-6425)
    - Clifford H. Davis v. United States (Box-folder 46: 71-6481)
    - Charles D. Braden v. 30th Judicial Circuit Court of Kentucky (Box-folder 46: 71-6516)
    - Marion P. Morris, on behalf of Linda Morris v. Elliot L. Richardson, Secretary of Health, Education and Welfare (Box-folder 46: 71-6698)
    - James Chaffin v. LeRoy Stynchcombe, Sheriff of Fulton County (Box-folder 46: 71-6732)
    - Felipe Juarez Hurtado v. United States (Box-folder 46: 71-6742)
    - David X. Fontaine v. United States (Box-folder 46: 71-6757)
    - Donald Paul Lubin v. Leonard Panish, Registrar-Recorder, County of Los Angeles (Box-folder 46: 71-6852)
    - David Moor v. County of Alameda (Box-folder 46: 72-10)
    - Roosevelt F. Palmore v. United States (Box-folder 47: 72-11)
    - Frank F. Murch v. Robert H. Mottram (Box-folder 47: 72-55)
    - Marilyn Cool v. United States (Box-folder 47: 72-72)
    - Georgia v. United States (Box-folder 47: 72-75)
    - Delores Norwood v. D. L. Harrison (Box-folder 47: 72-77)
    - United States v. Chicago, Burlington & Quiney Railroad Company (Box-folder 47: 72-90)
    - Lewis S. Tollett v. Willie Lee Henderson (Box-folder 47: 72-95)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People v. State of New York (Box-folder 47: 72-129)
    - Bob Bullock v. Diana Regester and White v. Regester, (2 folders) (Box-folder 47: 72-147)
      See also case 71-1476
    - Hoyt C. Cupp, Superintendent, Oregon State Penitentiary v. Daniel P. Murphy (Box-folder 47: 72-212)
    - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company v. Wichita Board of Trade (Box-folder 48: 72-214)
      See also case 72-433
    - Arthur Levitt, as Commissioner of the State of New York, and Ewald B. Nyquist, as Commissioner of Education of the State of New York v. Committee for Public Education & Religious Liberty (Box-folder 48: 72-269)
      See also cases 72-270, and 72-271
    - Warren M. Anderson, as Majority Leader and President pro tem of New York State Senate v. Committee for Public Education and Religious Liberty (Box-folder 48: 72-270)
      Found in case 72-269. See case 72-269 and 72-271.
    - Cathedral Academy v. Committee for Public Education and Religious Liberty (Box-folder 48: 72-271)
      Found in case 72-269. See cases 72-269 and 72-270.
    - United States v. State Tax Commission of Mississippi (Box-folder 48: 72-350)
    - Weinberger v. Hynson, Westcott & Dunning, Inc. (Box-folder 48: 72-394)
      See also case 72-414
    - Hynson, Westcott, and Dunning Incorporated v. Caspar W. Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box-folder 48: 72-414)
      Found in case 72-394
    - Pittsburgh Press Company v. The Pittsburgh Commission on Human Relations (Box-folder 48: 72-419)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission v. Wichita Board of Trade (Box-folder 48: 72-433)
      Found in case 72-214
    - Grace Sloan, as State Treasurer of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Alton J. Lemon (Box-folder 48: 72-459)
    - Federal Power Commission v. Memphis Light, Gas and Water Division (Box-folder 48: 72-486)
      See also case 72-488
    - Texas Gas Transmission Corporation v. Memphis Light, Gas and Water Division (Box-folder 48: 72-488)
      Found in case 72-486
    - McDonnell Douglas Corp. v. Green (Box-folder 48: 72-490)
    - John W. Vlandis, Director of Admissions, the University of Connecticut v. Margaret Marsh Kline and Patricia Catapano (Box-folder 49: 72-493)
    - CIBA Corporation v. Caspar W. Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box-folder 49: 72-528)
      See also case 72-555
    - United States Department of Agriculture v. Jacinta More (Box-folder 49: 72-534)
      See also case 72-848
    - United States and Interstate Commerce Commission v. Students Challenging Regulatory Agency Procedures (Box-folder 49: 72-535)
      See also case 72-562
    - Caspar Weinberger, Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare v. Bentex Pharmaceutical, Inc. (Box-folder 49: 72-555)
      See also case 72-528
    - Aberdeen and Rockfish Railroad Company v. Students Challenging Regulatory Agency Procedures (SCRAP) (Box-folder 49: 72-562)
      Found in case 72-535
    - Elmer O. Cady v. Chester J. Dombrowski, (2 folders) (Box-folder 50: 72-586)
    - State of Oklahoma v. Archie L. Mason and Margaret R. Mason (Box-folder 50: 72-606)
      See also case 72-654